You are pets with eyes de jewels, the Jewelpets
Born to become friends with the humans
Now, go and learn the arts de magic to bring joy to the humans
Yes~
With sparkling hearts
we Jewelpets
Sparkle, sparkle
do our Jewelflash
and make every-everyone
happy!
Each and every girl is a great magician
Tinkle, tinkle, Jewel Flash
Happy ☆ Tinkle
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  tobikiri no
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  I wanna see a
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  yume o mite
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  wonderful dream
Tonde tonde mirai e
Flying, flying to the future
Ready Go Ready Go Ready Go
Happy ☆ Tinkle!
Presented by Critter-Subs
Onna no ko wa dare mo, sekaijuu de
Every single girl in the world
tatta hitotsu no Jewel yo
is like a unique Jewel
Jishin o nakushitara, kagami no naka
When they lose their courage, they turn to a mirror
Jumon tonae, hashiridasou
cast a spell on themselves and start to run
Zenshin! Henshin!
Moving ahead! Transforming!
Tension agemasho!
Raising the tension!
Sono yasashisa, yuuki ga mahou ni naru yo
With that kindness their courage turns into magic
Lucky ☆ Lucky ☆  omoikitte
Lucky ☆ Lucky ☆  dashing forward
Lucky ☆ Lucky ☆  habataite
Lucky ☆ Lucky ☆  flapping their wings
Kitto kuru Miracle
A miracle is gonna happen for sure
Ready Go Ready Go
Chance tourai!
Your chance is now!
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  tobikkiri no
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  I wanna see a
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  yume o mite
Happy ☆ Happy ☆  wonderful dream
Tonde tonde mirai e
Flying, flying to the future
Ready Go Ready Go Ready Go
Happy ☆ Tinkle!
This program is presented by the following sponsors
A request from Ruby ♥
Please turn up the lights and don't sit too close to the screen.
Ok, it's my turn now
This is a story, that my big brother told me
The lights were on in the arts room, even though nobody should have been inside
And when they were turned off
Who is there?
Who turned off the lights?
Did you know that there are seven mysteries like that in our school?
I heard there's a stairway de twelve steps that has a thirteenths step at night
They say you can hear the music room's piano play at night too
That sounds interesting
How about we look into those mysteries tonight?
What do you say, Akari?
Akari?
Oh jeez, that was scary
How can they stay so calm while talking about those things
A~kari~~chan
H- hey, you scared me
I'm the one that was scared here
I don't like been scared
You know, you know
Tour-sama is holding a event at the academy tonight
Let's hurry and join too
An event?
That sounds like fun
The mysterious night, Doki ☆ Doki!
Welcome
Ladies and Gentlemen
We will now begin with our main event
The magic academy, seven mysteries contest
Tour
How in the world did you come up with that?
I found this book in the library
So I found out about the seven mysteries that have existed in this school since long ago
The seven mysteries are written down on those papers
I'd like you to look into them
"The seven fantasies"?
Sounds good, doesn't it?
You two aren't scared at all?
Don't worry Akari-chan
If something happens, we can just use magic
That won't be possible, lady
We got a new moon tonight
New moon?
What about it?
You see, you can't use magic on a new moon
So, we have no magic tonight?
Nicola?
T- this has nothing to do with my magic
A genius like me simply doesn't have any time to waste on something as trivial as a seven mystery contest
Please excuse us now-dechu
Are you scared?
W- why certainly not
It's no big deal for us-dechu
Let's stop this, Tour
Making the students do this alone on a new moon
What if something happens?
Well, that's why we will accompany them de course
Naturally the students that have the courage to look into all de the seven mysteries
Will be getting something as a reward
Did he say "reward"?
I can't tell you what exactly
But it's something star-shaped with "Jewel" in it's name
So, would you like to join in?
Could that be?
A Jewelstone?
Well then
The magic academy seven mystery contest
Starts now
Don't worry, Akari-chan
We got Tour-sama and Sulfur-sensei with us after all
Though he's lagging behind and shaking all over
Maybe he's scared
Of course not! I'm a teacher! I'm an adult!
There's no way I'd be scared by th-
I'm scared
You're being a scaredy-cat as always
If you knew that, then why did you drag me with you?
Let's just turn around and call this seven mysteries thing quits
No way
Give me a break!
Do you have any idea how often your
adventurous spirit has gotten me into trouble?
I wonder if he'll be alright
Alright, let's go
Yes~
The first mystery
Noise coming from an empty classroom
The moaning de a demon?
It says
A demon?
Which classroom could it mean?
This is it
The demon's moaning
Let's go
No, wait
Please don't leave me behind
It's this room
Could there be
A real demon inside there?
Geez loise, I can't stand by watching this any longer
De-chu-chuu~
You stink de garlic
So you actually are scared
Don't be silly
I am certainly not scared
Chu-rtainly
Make way you bunch de bafoons
Solving the riddle behind the seven mysteries, that is a job
For geniuses like us-dechu
Don't look
Headmaster?
Ah, it's just you
What are you doing here so late?
Same for you, Headmaster
As you can see
I'm using my muscle trainer that I got over the magic mail order
And why do you do that so late?
If Halite-sensei were to find out about this, she'd sure be angry
So I have to use it in secret when everybody else went home already
105K
106K
107K
Hey, wait a-
108K
109K
110K
111K
112K
113K
114K
115K
116K
This is too fa- ah
117K
118K
119K
120K
121K
122K
It's not like we ran because we were scared, right?
Sometimes you can just leave things to those dropouts-dechu
Exactly
It had absolutely nothing to do with us being scared
So the first de the seven mysteries
Was just the Headmaster
I wonder what's next
In a moonlit night
A devilish mist rises... it reads
A devilish mist?
Everybody that gets touched by that mist
Has his body melted
Scared?
I don't buy that!
Black mist
Stop it, make it stop please
This isn't mist
It's more like smoke
That is my anti-mushroom smoke
Anti-mushroom smoke?
It's damp down there, so they get inside some times
Seriously
First the Headmaster and now a fungal infestation?
Don't tell me the seven mysteries are all just things like this
A g-g-g-ghost
Oh-ho?
Did I scare you again?
Sorry, sorry
Headmaster
I'm going home now to catch some sleep
Make sure to lock the gate, alright?
Yes
There he goes
And we all got separated from each other
Wha-, what a shock
What now, Akari-chan?
We lost the others
Who's there?
Ah~ praise the heavens
All de you are unhurt
You must have been scared
But rest assured now
I shall accompany you
For you
That's so cool
I wonder if the others are alright
So cold
Third de the seven mysteries
Roaming the night
A student soaked to the bones
Could that be this?
So cold, so cold, so~ co~ld
So cold, so cold, so cold
What should we do, Sara?
We can't use magic tonight
W- what are you doing
To geni-chu-s like us?
And where you doing in there?
Th- that's because, earlier we...
A-choo-dechu
Achoo--dechu
Achoo-dechu-
I'll get scolded if I come home in soaked clothes
Can't we do something about that?
I have some spare clothes
Really?
You know
You're a lot nicer than I thought
They suit you
I really do hate you after all!
This seven mysteries thing
You think there's something to it-dachi?
I'm sure they are just made up-wan
I don't believe that stuff unless I see it with my own two eyes-geroppa
What on earth was that-dachi?
I've never seen such a huge Jewelpet before-wan
It's one de the mysteries-geroppa
Mystery number four
The multiplying statues
Still, this is overdoing it
What are you doing there?
We're making statues de the Headmaster-dana
And why so many and all the same?
They're not the same-desu~
This is the Headmaster at age one hundred forty eight
And that is the Headmaster on his two hundred eighty sixth birthday-desu~
We put all de our heart into making these for his birthdays-dana
The one for his one hundred twenty ninth was our masterpiece-desu~
No way
On the one hundred ninety forth we got his beard much better-dana
But I think we got his hair better on the two hundred forth-desu
But the roundness de his crystal ball is better on the one hundred first-dana
Excuse us
Fifth de the seven mysteries
The piano that plays on it's own at night, that must be this one
I don't hear a sound
Shhht!
Let's just wait for it-nyan
Seriously what point is there in it playing when nobody's around to hear it?
I bet it's a ghost that once wanted to be a pianist
So then why doesn't he play when he finally got an audience?
Nya~
Hey-hey-hey~hey
That sounds like a guitar playing in the empty music room-dachi
A ghost! A ghost is playing it-wan
It's one de the mysteries-geroppa
Bravo
What do you say?
Now you can call me a musician, I performed for somebody and even got standing ovations
Be quite-rin
Rin?
Just when I finally found a nice place to sleep
You had to show up and make a ruckus-rin
So it's Rin that makes the piano play at night?
There's nothing mysterious to this
Miria and the others
I hope they are alright
A cheeky nighttime breeze, don't you think?
Y- yes
You're so reliable, Sensei
Labula
Well, he is my partner after all
Thank you very much
Sixth de the seven mysteries
The stairway that leads to the school bells
Grows at night, it says
But I bet that mystery also has nothing to it once we look into it, right?
Well then we don't have to be scared
This is it
The mysteriously extending stairway
Yes
What's this?
There's no end to it
Labula
Goes on and on
What's up with that stairway?
It's a mystery
Unbelievable
Alright, go and climb it
Ladies and Gentlemen
No way, there's no way we can do that
We can't climb such a huge stairway
But if we don't look into it, we won't get a Jewelstone as a reward-nya
That's true, alright let's go Akari-chan
Ok
Hey Miria, let's go too
There's no turning back, it's for a Jewelstone after all
Fighto-nyan
Give it your all
Strange
Since earlier it feels like we're going in circles
Could it be that someone used a spell here?
You can't use magic today-nyan
So this time it's really the real deal? A real school mystery?
I'm so tiered, can't climb another step
Give up
More like seven torments
I'm not giving up
But it's really no use
Then take this
My special energy candy
Gimme gimme
Ruby-chan, reborn!
AlmostthereAlmostthere
Sara, what did you put in those candies?
Eucommia seeds from Tibet, Indian gecko and Japanese rat snake
AlmostthereAlmostthereAlmostthereAlmostthere
Don't overdo it Ruby
No way! I'm gonna investigate all the seven mysteries and get you a Jewelstone, Akari-chan
AlmostthereAlmostthereAlmostthereAlmostthere
The ceiling
Is just painted on
Looks like she punched through it
Ruby
Akari
Tinkle tinkle, magical charm
I really can't transform
It's over
Are you alright?
For a moment I forgot about this mechanism Tour had prepared for times de need
And rushed to your rescue
Sulfur-sensei
Actually, this was all there was to it
I'm sorry
Why did you do something like this?
You need a climax in every event
So in the end all de the seven mysteries were just made up
What a relief
But the last one really overdid it
I even had to use that safety device in the end
My sincerest apologies
Don't worry
Ruby and me are unhurt
And also
Somehow it was fun too
Sure was
So, about that reward
Of course, you all have earned it
The star-shaped thing with "Jewel" in it's name
I'm glad for you, everyone
Sulfur-sensei
Thank you so much
You were awesome too, Sulfur-sensei
When you caught Akari and Ruby you really were super awesome
Like a different man-nya
You're flattering me
You know, you know...
Actually I always thought that you're...
The stairway was the sixth mystery, right?
Aren't we one short?
The seventh is this
While searching for the seven mysteries
Someone will join your group
Someone?
Everyone
There you are, I was looking all over for you
Sulfur-sensei?
Yes?
S- so, then who is this Sulfur-sensei?
Who is this guy?
It was one wonderful night
So the seventh mystery was the only real one
You knew it from the start, didn't you?
Of course I did
My Sulfur is nowhere near as cool
Ok, time to give you your reward
The legendary "Jewelland star-cookies"
Star-cookies?
That's no Jewelstone
Jewelstone?
I only said "something star-shaped with Jewel in it's name", didn't I?
Tinkle tinkle
Elebore
Grila grila
Tinkle tinkle, Elebore-labu!
Yup, yup, that's my Sulfur
Sora ni rakugaki, kibou o ima ippai egakou
Scribbling at the sky, let's draw all de our wishes
Kitto mirai wa hate shinai yo
The future is limitless for sure
Ano sora to onaji kurai ni
Just like the sky
OK! Here we go!
Shiroi jitensha de, nobotta oka no ue
Riding a white train to the top de a hill
gyutto senobi o shite, tooku o mita
Standing on your tippy-toes, you look into the distance
Ano kumo no mukou, suteki na nanika ga
Beyond those clouds there must be something great
ashita no watashi o matteru ne
Waiting for the me de tomorrow
Kinou no ame ga kitto
Surely yesterdays rain
sora o konnani migaite kureta yo
just fell to make the sky sparkle like this
Sora ni rakugaki, omou mama ni chizu o kaitara
Scribbling at the sky, I'd draw a map as big as I want
kimi to yakusoku, kaze o kitte motte yukou
Like we promised, let's go together for a flight through the sky
Taiyou ga hora, yonde iru yo
Look, the sun is calling for us
OK! Here we go!
Hi, I'm Milky-desu~
Doki ☆ Doki ☆
-----------------------------------The secrets de the Jewelland!
I'm Luna-dana
Doki ☆ Doki ☆--------------------
The secrets de the Jewelland!
There are still a ton de secrets in the magic academy-dana
Did you all notice how really huge the academy is?
The insides de it have been enlarged with magic-dana
The headmaster did that to make room for all de the students-desu~
He's really incredible-dana
People that want to know more about the Jewelpets, can find lots de fun information on "ani.tv"-dana
So come on everybody, take a trip to Jewelland too-desu~
Preview
Did you hear, Akari-chan?
Next time they are teaching transformation magic
Transformation magic? Uwah~ I can't wait to try that
I wanna be a whale
I wanna be a flower-labu
And I a musical star
By the way, we're also getting some difficult homework
Why am I suddenly my dad?
Next time on Jewel Pet Tinkle
Papa's company, Doki ☆ Doki!
The magic time starts now
Tinkle tinkle, Jewel Flash
Each and every girl is a great magician
This program was presented by the following sponsors